[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scary thing happens to Carmen when she gets out of the bathtub in Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "A stereo falls into the bathtub", "incorrect_answers": ["She receives a threatening phone call", "She slips and hits her head", "She sees blood on the floor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Attica Prison was the locale of a 1975 riot that resulted in 38 deaths.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Cameron was so immersed in the movie Titanic that he actually spent more time with the real Titanic than the passengers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chinese Crested dog is very timid.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vampire bats blood-sucking does not hurt the bitten animal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Babys real name in the romance movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Frances", "incorrect_answers": ["Francesca", "Francine", "Frankie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The establishment of the Democratic Peoples Republic of Korea in this year set the official beginning of North Koreas history.", "correct_answer": "1948", "incorrect_answers": ["1940", "1950", "1945"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these things will not help you to get in touch with your neighbours PC.", "correct_answer": "Cache server", "incorrect_answers": ["Hub", "Router", "Network card"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bigfoot of Florida is known by this name.", "correct_answer": "Skunk Ape", "incorrect_answers": ["Ocala Beast", "Swamp Beast", "Miami Monster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actors Dolph Lundgren, Lena Olin, and Ann Margaret hail from this Scandinavian country that joined the European Union in 1995.", "correct_answer": "Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Norway", "Estonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which member of the High Noon crew was blacklisted because of the McCarthy hearings?", "correct_answer": "The director", "incorrect_answers": ["The musical director", "The cinematographer", "The executive producer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title to this Credence Clearwater Revival tune: Bad Moon ____.", "correct_answer": "Rising", "incorrect_answers": ["Falling", "Setting", "in Aquarius"]}]